

alefiya.murtuza@gmail.com

Dubai, UAE

Alefiya Hozefa

UX/UI Designer





Tools

Figma

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Sketch

Invision

Professional Skills

Design System

Design Thinking

Prototyping

Wireframes and

Micro Interactions

User Research

Moodboards

UX Design Strategist

About me

I am a usability designer, researcher and analyst with 3+ years of experience in the field of user experience (UX) and user-centered design (UCD). I help companies to excel and boost its identity, services and applications in the digital phase.

My expertise in design tools such as Sketch, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe illustrator and Figma enables me to create high-fidelity designs that effectively communicate design concepts to stakeholders.

Work Experience

Senior Product Designer







- May 2024- Present
- Created complete design system for "Aamia", with design tokens to improve flexibility.
- Designed the wallet, subscription and profile (3/5) modules of the "Aamia" project.
- Conducted user testing (card sorting, treejack testing), refining information architecture and improving navigation by 30%.

Super Future Technology

Full Time







- · Headed the SF Chat IM project a chat application with crypto transfer feature.
- Created the **Design System** for SF Chat IM completed the whole mobile application.
- Conducted stakeholder discussions, transforming feature-oriented requirements into actionable design backlogs.
- UX/ UI Designer
- Dubai
- **January 2023- May 2023**
- Led UX workshops with stakeholders, clarifying requirements and reducing iteration
- Created wireframes and moodboards for a crypto trading application for ROK market.
- Conducted UX assessments of existing digital products, identifying usability gaps.

Associate UX Designer

Full Time





- **a** Jan 2022 December 2022
- Designed various features for the Artaah mobile application.
- Collaborated with developers and product managers to implement user-centered UI designs with pixel-perfect execution.
- Created wireframes and interactive prototypes based on requirements, improving usability by 15% through iterative design

Graphic Designer/Content Creator

Full Time

Bravura Advertising LLC



- **a** April 2018 August 2020
- Styled the company profile and branding for various organizations including logos.
- Planned, managed and created advertising and promotional materials for events.

Education

Foundation of UX Design

Full Time

Full Time

Coursera



October 2021 - December 2022

BA (Hons) Media, Advertising and PR

a July 2011 - June 2014

Usability Testing

Problem Solving

Information Architecture

Lanuages

- **English**
- Urdu
- Hindi
- Gujarati

Middlesex University

Dubai